Number: 3
Address: <ORGANIZATION>ACORD<ORGANIZATION>° V EVIDENCE OF PROPERTY IN<PERSON>S<PERSON>URANCE DATE(<OTHER>IIMIDDIYYYY<OTHER>) 5/31/2016 COVERAGE AFFORDED BY THE POLICIES BELOW. THIS EVIDENCE THIS EVIDENCE OF PROPERTY INSURANCE IS ISSUED AS A MATTER OF INFORMATION ONLY AND CONFERS NO RIGHTS UPON THE ADDITIONAL INTEREST NAMED BELOW. THIS EVIDENCE DOES NOT AFFIRMATIVELY OR NEGATIVELY AMEND EXTEND OR ALTER THE OF INSURANCE DOES NOT CONSTITUTE A CONTRACT BETWEEN THE ISSUING INSURER(S) AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OR PRODUCER AND THE ADDITIONAL INTEREST. AGENCY PHONE COMPANY <LOCATION>West Bend Mutual Insurance Co 1900 South 18th Ave<LOCATION> <CONSUMER_GOOD>West Bend WI<CONSUMER_GOOD> 53095—7995 
Address: #CANCELLATION DELIVERED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE POLICY PROVISIONS. SHOULD ANY OF THE ABOVE DESCRIBED POLICIES BE CANCELLED BEFORE THE ADDITIONAL INTEREST "“5 AND ADDRESS <ORGANIZATION>Johnson Bank Its Successors<ORGANIZATION> and/or Assigns PO Box 3 9653 <PERSON>Solon<PERSON> OH 44139—0653 
Address: COMPANY <ORGANIZATION>West Bend Mutual Insurance Co 1900 South 18th Ave<ORGANIZATION> <OTHER>West Bend WI<OTHER> 53095—7995 
