Number: 4
Address: REGARDING YOUR HOMEOWNERS POLICY- GOLD STAR SPECIAL DELUXE FOR YOUR PROPERTYAT. 1761 <LOCATION>OREGON ST RACINE WI<LOCATION> 53405 
Address: INSURED - MIVSHEK <PERSON>DAVID<PERSON> & <LOCATION>URBAN JAMIE P 1761 OREGON ST RACINE WI<LOCATION> 53405-3635 
Address: #<CONSUMER_GOOD>AMERICAN FAMILY INSURANCE 1900<CONSUMER_GOOD> <LOCATION>LATHROP<LOCATION> AVE <LOCATION>RACINE<LOCATION> WI 53405-3707 
Address: #129-045 PABO28 JOHNSON BANK ITS SUCCESSORS AND/OR ASSIGNS PO BOX 39653 <LOCATION>SOLON<LOCATION> OH 44139-0653 
